Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lisadbarnett (LinkedIn) lisabarnett.net (Other) littlespoon.com (Other)

Top Skills

Competitive Analysis Acquisition Integration Private Equity

Honors-Awards

Collegiate Awards & Honors Forbes 30 Under 30 - 2017 (Venture Capital)

Lisa Barnett

Co-Founder, President & CMO- We're hiring! New York

Summary

Lisa Barnett is the Co-Founder & President of Little Spoon, the fastest growing direct-to-consumer children's food and nutrition company reinventing the modern parent's experience of keeping their child healthy. She has been recognized as one of the 'Women Changing the Food Industry' by Well + Good, and by Forbes as 30 Under 30 in Venture Capital.

Prior to Little Spoon, Lisa spent nearly a decade as an investor in and operator at some of the world's top consumer brands including Estee Lauder Companies, Calvin Klein, Weight Watchers and a number of other Fortune 500 Companies. As an investor, she was focused on investing in brand-driven startups aimed at transforming the everyday life of consumers in the wellness, health and CPG space.

Experience

Little Spoon
Co-Founder, President & CMO
January 2017 - Present (3 years 8 months)
Greater New York City Area

We're here to make this parenting thing a little easier. Little Spoon creates fresh, organic and high quality meals and nutritional products for babies and kids and ships them directly to your door across the nation. Over 2 million meals and counting.

Check out our parenting platform and community, Is This Normal (www.isthisnormal.co).

Sherpa Foundry
Partner
January 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 2 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

Forbes 30 under 30 Venture Capital. Sherpa Foundry, part of the venture capital firm, Sherpa Ventures, works with Fortune 500 companies to incubate and develop new businesses and products, as well as invest and facilitate partnerships with the world's leading startups and founders.

Dorm Room Fund

Partner

December 2014 - April 2016 (1 year 5 months)

Greater Philadelphia Area / SF Bay Area

Led investments in top student entrepreneurs across universities. Dorm Room Fund is a subsidary of First Round Capital

Maveron LLC

Investor Fellow

September 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 4 months)

San Francisco Bay Area

Maveron is a SF and Seattle based venture capital firm that invests exclusively in consumer companies. Founded in 1998 by Dan Levitan and Howard Schultz, Maveron's portfolio includes eBay, Capella Education, drugstore.com, Shutterfly, Everlane, Julep, zulily, and General Assembly.

Maveron focuses on early stage and seed technology investments with particular emphasis on web-enabled consumer services, education and health & wellness.

The Estée Lauder Companies Inc.
Growth | Corporate Transactions
August 2013 - September 2014 (1 year 2 months)

Drive efforts for Estee Lauder brands enter and scale high growth channels - retail, DTC, ecommerce, and everything in between

LaunchPad Long Island

Greater New York City Area

Advisor

December 2012 - August 2014 (1 year 9 months)

LaunchPad is an incubator, business accelerator and coworking community designed to help start-ups and early-stage companies. The goal is to help entrepreneurs and companies build a viable product, launch fast and prepare for growth.

I focused on e-commerce and DTC companies, advising on customer acquisition.

The Boston Consulting Group (BCG)

2 years 2 months

Consultant

August 2013 - September 2013 (2 months)

Greater New York City Area

Worked with Fortune 500 retail and consumer clients helping them to grow by entering new markets and customer segments, consumer insights, and redefining the customer experience

Associate

August 2011 - July 2013 (2 years)

Deloitte Consulting

Business Analyst Summer Scholar; Strategy & Operations June 2010 - August 2010 (3 months)

Developed target operating model as part of the outsourcing of the asset management operations of a global bank

ACP Magazines

Digital Marketing Manager
July 2009 - April 2010 (10 months)

Sydney, Australia

ACP Magazines is the umbrella company for Australian Geographic Outdoor, Cosmopolitan, CLEO, Women's Weekly, Gourmet Traveler, and many other magazines in Australia. I focused on brand and digital marketing, subscriber retention and new channel growth.

1800flowers.com
Digital Marketing Associate (intern)
June 2008 - August 2008 (3 months)

Education

University of Pennsylvania
Bachelor of Arts, Communication, Marketing/Consumer Psychology

University of Pennsylvania - The Wharton School

Master of Business Administration (MBA)